What? You were playing Wii Cross until 4 a.m.?
Yeah, I showed it to my grandma and she got hooked.
The deal was, Loser had to peel tangerines and I lost.
Now my hands are all orange, look!
Ew!
Yeesh.
There's this stuff called soap?
Yeah, thanks.
So you were saying we don't need to battle each other anymore?
Hm?
Yeah. The world can make room for one more Eternal Girl.
Both of us can have our wishes come true.
But I don't have one.
I haven't even thought about it.
Come on!
Let's go!
Hey! Wait up, you guys!
Hey!
Once and Hero Lake, what is this?
It's your favorite scene.
Them all
I'm so happy that you can grab closer to the baby
What should you choose with what kind of information if you could do it
No one can bite, but I'm never missing
humorous leaves泉 of 1997, and mom can try to演じ
How many words of to make your smile lonely
I don't want to forget the real world, I don't want to change it
That's why I don't want to know now
Tell her, Hanayo
Yes, but L-Rigs are attracted to each other
We can identify selectors on-site, right over there, for example
Iona Urazoe
What about her? Is she a selector? She's on TV a lot, even had a new single just dropped
The girl next to her is one, too
Really? She's in magazines a lot, too
It's... oh, come on, it's on the tip of my tongue
Akira!
That's her!
Hey, look, it says here she goes to Gochu High
Wait, which high school? Say it again?
Uh, what?
Maybe this isn't the best time
Come on, better now than never
But I get first dibs, okay?
I'll set up matches for after school and-
It's her! Akira!
Wow!
Just like the pictures, she's so pretty
Now's our chance! Let's go challenge her!
Wait! Akira, please!
I'm begging you!
You have to battle me!
Huh?
That girl is... a selector?
Uh, you're... selectors, too?
Who are these losers?
Akira's too busy to sign autographs right now, so buzz off!
Uh, no! Wait, I just want-
Thanks for being my fan!
If you want something autographed, then let's go someplace private!
You guys, too!
What? Us?
Come on, Roku!
Akira's too nice to her fans!
Here!
Perfect!
Alright!
With all these selectors, I'm so lucky!
Or as I like to say...
Akira's too nice to her fans!
Um... I don't, uh...
So let's get a battle done before class starts, okay?
Which one of you girls is up first?
I am!
Alrighty then!
What's your name?
My name is Hitoy!
Love it!
Now let's get this party started, yo!
One nice and friendly battle ready to open!
I assume you both are wondering what you're doing here.
When a battlefield is opened, any Eternal Girl candidates nearby are drawn inside.
Well, that's late!
Wait!
That sounds like...
Tama!
Hey!
You're gonna get my hair all goofed up if you keep doing that!
Look, it's starting!
I'm first!
Guess it's now or never!
Let's go!
Battle start!
Are you ready, Midoriko?
Yeah!
Leave it to me!
My L-Rig is Aki-lucky, too!
Meet Piriluk!
Go Stompy-Stompy on them, okay?
Understood.
A green deck versus a blue deck, huh?
There's a possibility this Hito-e girl may have the upper hand.
Draw!
Energy charge, Midoriko!
Now grow!
First up, another Sparrow!
Sparrow, attack!
Whoa!
She's starting off strong!
It worked?
All I have to do is keep Midoriko growing so we don't lose momentum!
Oh, what a meanie!
Whatever shall we do?
You've got this, Piriluk.
Just grow and we'll take her out!
But those green decks really are unnerving.
There's no telling what cards Little Miss Four Eyes has in her hand.
To make things less scary, I think I'll just have her throw one of those cards away.
All right, Hito-e, I'm gonna choose one of your cards at random.
Hope it's one you can afford to play without!
Spell!
Too bad!
Okay, not looking!
Oh yeah!
I'm betting that's a Level 3 card, isn't it?
Oh, it's not so hard!
But those green decks really are unnerving.
There's no telling what cards Little Miss Four Eyes has in her hand.
To make things less scary, I think I'll just have her throw one of those cards away.
All right, Hito-e, I'm gonna choose one of your cards at random.
Hope it's one you can afford to play without!
Spell!
Too bad!
Kay, not looking.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. I'm betting that's a level three card, isn't it?
Expose.
Bullseye!
Aki-luck again!
The card just vanished.
It's one of the blue deck's top strategies.
A player can force their opponent to lose a card.
That sucks.
Barrel, let's roll!
And while you're at it, freeze Hito-e's sparrow.
Look at me!
Aw, your cute little birdie's been put on ice till the next turn.
Oh, Midoriko, what should I do?
I only have two cards left.
If I mess up...
Just calm down, Hito-e!
If that's already got you freaking out,
wait till you see the other stuff I've got in store.
Go, Karolak!
Arts.
Peeping Analyze.
Seen this one?
Super handy.
I pick a level, then you throw away all your cards that match it.
Aw, my cards!
I wonder what I should pick.
Let's see.
Level...
Two...
This is bad.
She can read her.
Three...
Four...
Yeah, that's the one.
All level four cards?
Go, Bapai!
New game!
Jeez!
Pull it together!
Not that you have any hope of winning,
but now you got me wondering
why you want to become an Eternal Girl!
Let's find out your little wish, shall we?
The poor thing
She has no friends
Nobody loves Ito-A
She doesn't have it
Ito-A, come on
We're still in this
So ignore her and don't give up
Loser
Screw this
Izuki, what?
I'm going to put a stop to her right now
I know, I'll interfere just like Kazuki did when you and I had our battle
That should do the trick
It won't
Why not?
Kazuki didn't stop the battle the last time
It was the teacher
And that was only because of an irregular occurrence
An interruption by someone who knew nothing about the cards
Also
If ever a battle is stopped on purpose, a huge penalty is issued
A penalty?
What about one for the way Akira's been playing?
She hasn't broken any rules thus far
Yeah, but
Dang, this game
It's horrible
How could she?
Come on
Yeah, Pirilac
Finish this
Ito-A
I
Don't have any life cloth left
You can't give up now
Take guard against the attack
Why
I'm just gonna lose anyway
What's the U?
Believe in me
Please
Ito-A
The game's over
Akira won
I'm sorry
I tried, but
I can't
Midoriko begged me to fight
But I gave up
And now she's the one paying for it
It's all my fault
Um
You okay?
Ito-A
So
Who wants to battle next?
Oh
Already, Pirilac?
Crud
She falls asleep so quickly
Well then
We'll just have to battle tomorrow
Okay?
Can I get your cell number?
Well
You see
I don't have a cell phone
No way
That is so old school
What's yours?
I, um
Yosuke
Gotta go
We're super late for class
I am not letting you go
Until you give up the digits
Right now
Ruko
Did you get in trouble
For being tardy?
Yeah
But I just had to stand out
In the hall
It was math class
So I was lucky
Or sorry
I mean
Aki-lucky
Oh god
Make me cringe
Damn
Akira's a monster
She'd probably thrash me
As hard as that other girl
Well why did you give her
Your phone number then?
What choice did I have?
She wasn't gonna let us go
Oh
Hey
I could battle Akira
If you want me to
Don't worry
As long as you don't agree
To a battle
You'll be fine
Yeah
Good point
I was watching from the outside
And you're right
She's strong
Yeah
But that Hitoe girl
Wasn't bad either
I didn't know all the
Eternal girl candidates
Would be this tough
I wonder
If I can win it all
Sure you can
I mean
All you need to do
Is update your deck
But that means
We'd have to go
To the card shop
Um
Yeah
Unless that's a problem
No
Oh I've never been to one before
Can I go?
Sure
We'll all go together
Cool
Wow
I never knew there was a card shop
In this neighborhood
So Kazuki
You're really an expert
On all this stuff
Aren't you?
Yeah
I was playing Wee Cross
Before it got popular
With everyone else
When I recommended it to Yuzuki
Her deck had Hanayo in it
Right Yuzuki?
Right
Well
We're here
It's so big
Wow
This place takes cards
Pretty seriously
Hey Kazuki
We just got a new Wee Cross
Set in today
And Yuzuki tagged along too
Been a while
Yeah
Guess so
We're hoping to update
Yuzuki's deck today
Would you mind giving us
Some advice?
Course not
You know I'd do anything
For you Kazuki
Just tell me what you need
And I'm all yours
Let's see
Yuzuki's deck is
Red Ambition
So
In my opinion
It should cycle a lot better
With an Adamosphere
Oh yeah
I think I've heard of that one
It's a Signy from the new series
Right?
Yep
But there aren't any singles
On the collector's market yet
All these packs and nothing
What about these cards?
Nah
They won't really mesh well
With the rest of Yuzuki's deck
Well if you don't want this one
Do you think I could have it then?
Huh?
Well tell me if I'm doing this wrong
But it looks like if I use this little buddy
In my deck
I can search non-colored Signys
Oh yeah
You sure can
I'm surprised you know that
For a newbie
You're good
Guess we'll have to wait for someone
To sell a single
For now you'll just have to get better
With the deck you have
All right
It's your turn
I'll draw this one and charge
And now grow
Hey wait a minute
Show me your hand
Level 2 again?
You know you'd probably do better
If you strategize your growing
Yeah but
You have to
Your game play is way too straightforward
What's wrong with being straightforward?
I'm going to bed
Yusuke
I'm going to marry Kazuki one day
Oh how cute
Ew that's icky
Yeah brothers and sisters
Can't get married you dumb baby
Huh?
If you want to
Then there's something wrong with you
You're a weirdo
I'm a weirdo?
Yusuke
Too straightforward
What's wrong with that?
It just means I'm honest doesn't it?
How exactly is that supposed to be a bad thing?
Akira
So who's going to battle me tomorrow?
Yuzu pool
Or Ruru
I can't lose to her
And I won't
Wait there Tama okay?
I feel really sorry for that Hitoi girl
But still
It's funny
But I
I feel like I have to battle Akira myself
Even if I know I can't win
No I was just thinking out loud
I don't even have a wish
So why would I get into a battle with her?
Do battle!
I can't think of anything that I'd even wish for
Except grandma living a long time
That's a wish right?
Oh hey
You're not hanging with Kazuki today?
No
He had something to do
Oh yeah like what?
That's your phone
Of course
Geez Akira
Obsessed much?
This last text says she's on her way here now to find us
Oh my gosh Rue
Let's find some place to hide
Yeah
Right
But where?
Hey
Let's go in here
Karaoke?
Yeah they've got private rooms
Where Akira won't be able to find us
I've never done karaoke before
Like
What song should I even sing?
Figure it out when we get inside
No wait a minute
Hang on
You gotta plan these things out first
You know
Like strategize for the big fight
Strategize?
Mm-hmm
Yeah cause
Kazuki
That's the girl who works at the card shop
Um
Momoka
Isn't it?
Wow they look pretty cozy together don't they?
Hey
Maybe they're on a date
Shut up
What?
Is something wrong?
You know what?
I don't get you
Maybe it's cause you don't have a wish
After that battle the other day
You saw what's at stake in how people like Hitoe can get hurt
Are you taking this seriously?
Yes!
Of course I am!
Don't think like that!
Why not?
Cause I have no idea what you're thinking Ruko!
Yeah well
That makes two of us
But
I wish I knew
That'd be nice
Please
I'm begging you
For Majorico's sake
Please
Have a battle with me
You have to
Me?
There you are
Goodness
Have you been hiding from me you naughty girl?
Guess I'm just lucky I found ya
Aki-lucky
Hey Akira
Come on down here
This battle will be flippin' epic
We are gonna have so much fun
But I'll have more
Cause I'm gonna beat the living crap out of you
Bring it
I've got some stress I need to work off
I'll have fun
.
Thank you.
無限の果てまでは進むしかない 自分で選んだ未来だから 届かない今すぐも揺れる陽炎を いつか取り戻す笑顔の場所を
次回の動画でお会いしましょう 次回の動画でお会いしましょう 次回の動画でお会いしましょう